passengers on a Spirit Airlines flight
thought Spirit was like a fake airline
oh it's fake they were on a flight
headed to New Jersey and freaked out
because they should have there was a bat
on the plane it got video and viral as
it should and spirit offered the guy who
filmed at $50.00 travel voucher that
sounds lower that's all they had in the
check that was the cost of the flight
$50 yeah that bought that particularly
what is in New York don't expect
somebody to get rabies on a Spirit
Airlines flight it was the guy's
emotional support bat
it is the fence oh wait it's like the
idea of the bat going through TSA yeah
like getting patted down being like I
you know what let me just drink this
cows blood before I go it out oh yeah
got it I've had doctor take out my iPad
I just I just I just think it's like
people were freaking out like 30 minutes
into the flight like from the moment I
bought the ticket for Spirit Airlines
freaking out yeah but even the bat is
freaking out you can fly
these that he woke up I want spirit yes
oh by the way this is exciting we got
the bat live via satellite you said oh
let's check check it on the bat right
now bat are you there I didn't I didn't
know you were back to Dracula yes I
switched back when they turned on the
seatbelt sign blah let me tell you it
was a rough night David
I had a middle seat I've slept in
coffins more comfortable $40 for a
carry-on I thought I was a bloodsucker
okay thanks Dracula why was I on this
plate we'll have a medical device
salesman yeah can I stop you I feel this
is a to finish that bit I bailed out on
he stayed in there now that most people
wear capes you know no we had to get
that cape like an hour ago
[Music]
you